Guide to the Goddard Lieberson Papers
Yale University Music Library
- Correspondence, 1939-1977
  - Lettered correspondence
    - Savory & Moore Ltd. (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Sawaki, Masao (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Saxe, Edward L. (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Sayao, Bidu (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Sayer, Mr. & Mrs. Arthur R. (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Sayres, Julia (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Schary, Dore (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Scheel, Gerd W. (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Scheftel, Stuart (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Schein, Joy (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Schein, Harvey (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Scherer, Bob (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Schiff Terhune Inc. (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Schiller, Jonathan (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Schissel, Jack (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Schlesinger, Arthur (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Schlesinger, Barry (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Schlesinger, Lora (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Schling, Mrs. Max (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Schling, Max Jr. (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Schmidt, Peter (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Schmidt, Simon (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Schnaoller, Mrs. J (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Schnee, Thelma (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Schneider, Alexander (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Schneider, John A. ("Jack") (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Schneider, Mischa (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Schneider, Paul (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Schneider, Sasha (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Schoenberg, Arnold & Gertrud (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Schoenberg, Ronald & Lawrence, & Nuria Nono (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Scholder, Fritz (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - School of American Research (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - School Service Bureau (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Schott, Webster (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Schuitema, William & Christine (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Schuller, Gunther (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Schuman, William (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Schwann Record & Tape Guide (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Schwartz, Albert (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Schwartz, Arthur (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Schwartz, Douglas & Nita (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Schwartz, Raymond (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Schwartz, Steven D. (Schwarty) (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Schweitzer (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Scofield, Paul (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Scott, Ellie (Mrs. Winfield) (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Scott, Francis II (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Scott, Howard H. (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Scottish Union House (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Sears, Eleo (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Sears, Roebuck, & Co. (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Seattle Public Schools (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Seattle Symphony (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Securities & Exchange Commission (SEC) (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Seeger, Charles (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Seeger, Peter (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Segelstein, Irwin (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Seidlitz, Richard M. (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Seidmann, Ginette (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Seitlin, Charlotte (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Seitlin, Percy (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Seitz, A. (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Sekine, Michiko (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Selkowitz, Milton (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Selznick, Irene (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Serkin, Irene & Rudolf (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Service Diaries (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Sessions, Roger (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Sevareid, Eric (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Sevilla, Jean-Paul (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Sewell, Katharine (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Sewell, Tom (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Shade, James (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Shahn, Ben (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Shakespeare, Frank J. (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Shapiro, Nat (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Shapiro, Stanley (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Shaw, Arnold (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Shaw, Irwin (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Shaw, Virginia (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Shaw, William (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Shearson Hayden Stone Inc. (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Shepard, Thomas (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Shestack, Jerome (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Shestopal, George (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Shevelove, Burt (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Shevey, Sandra (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Shirley, George (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Shivers, Allan (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Shore, Dinah (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Shore, Paul (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Shorewood Packaging Corporation (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Shouse, Jouett (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Shrimpton, Jean (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Shukat, Scott (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Siddons, Mrs. (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Siegmeister, Elie (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Silipigini, Alfredo (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Silsby, Jessica (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Silverman, Fred (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Silvers, Phil (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Silvert, Martin (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Simon, George T. (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Simon, John (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Simon, Neil (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Simon, Paul (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Simon, Simone (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Sinatra, Frank & Barbara (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Singer, Richard (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Singher, Martial (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Sisters of Charity (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Sitwell, Edith (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Sitwell, Osbert (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Sitwell, Sacheverell (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Skinner, Cornelia Otis (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Slaff, George (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Slater, Joseph (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Slinger, C.D. (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Sloan, Alan (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Slonimsky, Nicolas (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Small, Arnold (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Smith, Carleton Sprague (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Smith, Harry E. (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Smith, James S. (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Smith, Mia (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Smith, Morgan (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Smith, Oliver (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Smith, Peter (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Smith, W. Eugene (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Smith, William (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - The Smithsonian Institution (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Snow, Charles P. (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Soames, Christopher (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Soble, Ellis B. (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Sochynsky, Mrs. R.W. (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Society of Photographic Scientists & Engineers (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Sokoloff, Boris & Nancy (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Solleveld, Coen (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Solo, Robert H. (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Solomon, Harold (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Solomons, Arnold L. (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Solters & Sabinson, Inc. (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Somer, Abraham ("Abe") (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Sondheim, Stephen (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Sony Corporation (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Souplet, Mr. & Mrs. Jacques (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Speculum Musicae (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Spellman, Cardinal Francis (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Spencer, Theodore (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Spewack, Bella (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Spivacke, Harold (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Spoken Arts, Inc. (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Spots Alive, Inc. (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Spray Clean (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Staatliche Kunsthalle (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Stafford, Jo (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Stanford University (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Stanley, Stan (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Stanton, Arthur (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Stanton, Frank (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Stanton, Frank (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Stapleton, Jean (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Stark, Ray (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Stavers, Gloria (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Steber, Eleanor (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Steelman, John R. (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Steinbeck, John (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Steinberg, Hans Wilhelm (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Steinberg, Saul (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Steinway, Mr. & Mrs. Henry Z. (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Steinway & Sons (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Steinweiss, Alex (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Steloff, Frances (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Stephens, Willis H. (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Stereo Review (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Sterling, Grace & Co. (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Sterling Manhattan CATV (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Stern, Mrs. A.R. (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Stern, Cohen & Burns (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Stern, Harold H. (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Stern, Isaac (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Stern, Philip van Doren (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Stevens, George Jr. (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Stevens, Risë (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Stevens, Roger L. (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Stevenson, Adlai (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Stewart, George (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Stewart, Lindsay (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Stewart, Serena (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Stichting Collectieve (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Stille, Clair US Agt. (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Stirling, James (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Stirling, Johnny (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Stirling, Magda & Patrick Petit (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Stirling, Susie (Mrs. William) (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Stogel, Leonard (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Stokowski, Leopold (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Stokowski, Leopold (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Stølen, Kr. P. (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Stone Ridge Kennels (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Stonzek, Morris (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Stothart, Robert (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Stralem, Mr. & Mrs. Donald (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Stratford Music Corporation (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Stratta, Ettore (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Stravinsky, Igor & Vera (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Streisand, Barbra (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Strouse, Charles (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Strouse, Dorothea (Mrs. Roger W.) (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - STUBS (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Stulberg, Gordon (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Styne, Jule (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Styne, Margaret (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Subber, Saint (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Suburbia, Inc. (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Suffolk Cooperative Library System (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Suffolk State School (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Sugar, Piero & Ladislao (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Sugi, Yutaka (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Sullivan, Ed (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Sullivan, Frank (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Sulzberger, Carol (Mrs. Arthur Ochs) (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - The Sunstone Press (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Supreme Mix (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Surovy, Walter (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Susquehanna (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Sutin, Thayer & Browne (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Sutton, Percy (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Swank Motion Pictures (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Swiss Bank Corporation (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Symphony for United Nations (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Syracuse University (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Szell, George (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Szigeti, Joseph ("Joska") (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Tait, Gunda (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Talley, James (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Tallon Karlweis, Ninon (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Tamayo, Olga (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Tanabe, Miss A. (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Tanaka, Masao & Chizuko (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Tang, Mr. & Mrs. Lin Yu (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Tannhausers (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Taplin, Frank E. (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Taubman, Martin H. (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Taylor, Arthur (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Taylor, Deems (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Taylor, Larry (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Taylor, Lebaron (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Tchelitchev, Pavlik (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Teifer, Gerald (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Telecip (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Teng, Cary C. (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - The Tennessean (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Tennis Indoors (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Tennis Tote (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Terrestris (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Tessler, Jack J. (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Theater Chamber Players (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Theatre Development Fund (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Theatre for Ideas, Inc. (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Theatre Incorporated (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Theatre de Lys (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Theatre Music Co. (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Theatre Projects Limited (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Thomas, Franklin A. (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Thomas, Nancy (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Thomas, Sheila (Mrs. Richard) (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Thomas Y. Crowell Company (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Thomson, Virgil (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Thompson, W. Robert (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Thorne, Francis (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Thurber, James (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Tietjen, Joan (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Tighe, Benedict (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Tillman Franks Enterprise (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Time Magazine (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Times Mirror (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Timmins, Mr. & Mrs. Jules (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Tippin, Ralph S. (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Tisch, Laurence Alan (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Tisch, Preston Robert (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Tobay Hadassah (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Tobin, Robert L.B. (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Toch, Ernst (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Torjusson, Sigrid (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Toscanini, Arturo (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Toscanini, Walter (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Tourel, Jennie (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Tourtellot, Arthur B. (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Town Tennis Members Club (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Towne Cleaners, Ltd. (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Townsend, Irving (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Trans World Airlines (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Traubel, Helen (Mrs. William Bass) (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Tree, Marietta (Mrs. Ronald) (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Tree, Ronald (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Troy-Bilt (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Truman, Harry S. (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Truman, Margaret (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Trumbull, Roy H. (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Tucker, Richard & Sara (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Turnbull & Asser Ltd. (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Turner Greenhouses (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Turner, Rev. Paul Tyler (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Twain, Norman (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Tynan, Kenneth (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Tyrrell, Jim (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Ullmann, Liv (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - UNC-TV (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Union de Cronistas de Teatro y Musica (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - United Artists Corporation (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - United Cerebral Palsy Fund (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - United Nations Educational, Scientific and Cultural Organisation (UNESCO) (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - United States Corporation Company (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - United States Council for World Affairs (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - United States Department of Justice (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - United States Department of the Interior (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - United States District Court (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - United States Embassy (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - United States Housing & Home Finance Agency (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - United States Military (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - United States Postal Service (USPS) (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - United States Trust Company (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - University of Hawaii (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - University of Miami (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - University of Missouri (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - University of New Mexico (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - University of Pennsylvania (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - University of Southern California (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - University Speakers Bureau (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - University of Washington (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - University of West Florida (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - University of Wyoming (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Urban, C.J. (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Ustinov, Peter & Pam (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Valando, Tommy (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Vallaro, Vic (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Vallée, Rudy (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Valjean, Nelson (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Vance, Sanders & Company, Inc. (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Van de Haar, Tony (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - vanden Heuvel, William J. (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - van Vechten, Carl (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Varèse, Edgar (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Variety Club (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Veneklasen, Paul S (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Venet, Steven (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Verdura, Inc. (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Vernon, William H. (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Verploeg, Marie (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Vidal, Gore (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Vidor, Charles (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Viertel, Peter (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - The Viking Press Inc. Publishers (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - The Village Voice (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Villa-Lobos, Mr. & Mrs. Heitor (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Villar, Charing & Luis (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Villarreal, Manuel (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Vinton, Bob & Dolly (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Vis, John (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Visibility Unlimited (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Vogue (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Volker, Mr. de la Harpe (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Vollmar, Theo (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - von Einem, Gottfried (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Vonnegut, Kurt Jr. (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - von Tobel, Rudolf (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Voskovec, George (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Waggoner, Walter (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Wagler, Mr. & Mrs. Nitya; Mr. & Mrs. Zoltan Radnoti (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Wagner, Alan (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Wagner College (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Wagner, Prager, Levy & Partners (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Wald, Jerry (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Wallach, Eli (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Wallace, Mrs. DeWitt (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Waller, John (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Wallerstein, David (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Wallerstein Edward ("Ted") (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Wallichs, Glenn (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Wallis, Sarah O'Neil (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Walpin, Gerald (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Walpole Woodworkers (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Walter, Bruno A. (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Walter, Bruno A. (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Walther, J. Barb. & Catherine (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Walton, Sir William and Lady (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Wanatabe, Misa (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Warburg, Edward M.M. (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Ward, John Owen (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Wargo, Marty (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Waring, Virginia Morley (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Warner Development Co., Inc. (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Warner, Francis (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Warner, Jane (Mrs. R. Miles) (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Warren, Gretchen (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Washington Houses Community Center (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Washington International Arts Letter (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - The Washington Post (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Waterbury Films Ltd. (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Waters, Edward N. (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Waugh, Alec (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Wax, Mo (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Waxman, Franz (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - W.B. Saunders Co. (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - WEA Distributing Corporation (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Weaver, Paul J. (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Webb, Candida J. (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Weber, Warren (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Wechsberg, Joseph (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - The Weeks School (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Weigl, Mrs. Karl (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Weil, Katherine (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Weinberg, Joel (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Weiner, Rosella (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Weinstock, Herbert (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Weisgal, Meyer W. (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Weisman, Julie (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Weissberger, L. Arnold (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Weisskopf, Victor & Ellen (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Weitzman, Ira (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Weizman, Chaim (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Welitch, Ljuba (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Wershba, Joseph (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Wesleyan University (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Westarbor (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Westinghouse Broadcasting Company, Inc. (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Weston, Paul (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Weston Productions (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Wexler (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Wheeler, Hugh (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Whipple, Hal (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Whitbread-Nolan, Inc. (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - White, Gilbert, Koch & Kelly (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - White, Granville (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - White Flower Farm (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - White, Frank (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Whitney, John Hay (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Whitney Museum of American Art (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Whitting, Frances (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Whyte Cotton, Dorothy (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Wick, Ted (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Widney, Stone (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Wiggins, Jim (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Wilder, Alec (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Wilder, Alec (oversized) (Box 81, Folder 2)
    - Wilder, Billy (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Wilder, Isabel (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Wilder, Thornton (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Wiley, John Mason (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Wilkie, David (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Wilkins, W.G. (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - William H. Strauss & Associates (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Williams, Andy (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Williams, Claudine (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Williams College (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Willson, Meredith & Rini (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Wilson, John C. (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Wilson, Thomas (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Wilson Transfer & Storage (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Wimpelmann, Christian (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Wimpelmann, Jan (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Windsor, Duke of (Edward VIII) (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Winterport Free Library (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Winzen, Father Damasus (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Wisner, Jimmy (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Wisner, Polly (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Witten, Laurence (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Witzer & Small Agency (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - WLAC-TV, Inc. (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - WNET/13 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Wolf Trap Foundation (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Wolfe, Ellen (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Wolff, Kurt (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Wolpert, Rudolph (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Women's American ORT (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Wong, Mabel (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Wood, Robert (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Wood, Wesley T. (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Woodward, O.B. ("Woody") (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Wookey, Richard (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Wool, Sheldon (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Woolford, Bill (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Woolford, Jeane (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - World Wide Specialties (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - World Wildlife Fund (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Wright, Robert & George Forrest (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - WSOK (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Wunderman, Ricotta & Kline, Inc. (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Wussler, Robert (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Wyngaard, Max (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Wynshaw, David (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Xerox Corporation (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Yale University (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Yale University (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Yale University Music Library (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Yamano Music Store (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Yankee Doodle Society (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Yarrowstalk (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Yatsuhashi, K. (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Yeager, Gerald A. (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Yeston's (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Yetnikoff, Walter (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Yokel, Alex (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Young Audiences, Inc. (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Young Men's & Young Women's Hebrew Association (YMHA, YWHA) (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Zadan, Craig (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Zaharoff, Floria Paci (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Zale, Charles (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Zanuck, Darryl (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Zarem, Robert M. (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Zeckendorf, William Jr. (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Ziegel, Olivier (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Zilboorg, Gregory (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Zimmer, Max J. (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Zinnemann, Fred (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Zinsser, William K. (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Zirato, Bruno & Carla (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Unidentified Name Correspondence (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence between Others (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence by subject
    Material in the Correspondence by Subject subseries relates to particular events or milestones in Lieberson's life and career - for example, congratulatory letters sent to Lieberson upon his promotion to director of Columbia Records.
    - Christmas cards, 1967-1977 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Christmas, 1967-1973 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Condolence letters to Brigitta Lieberson, A-E, 1977 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Condolence letters to Brigitta Lieberson, F-H, 1977 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Condolence letters to Brigitta Lieberson, H-L, 1977 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Condolence letters to Brigitta, L-O, 1977 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Condolence letters to Brigitta, P-R, 1977 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Condolence letters to Brigitta, S, 1977 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Condolence letters to Brigitta, T-Z, 1977 (Box 28, Folder 4)